https://nyphil.org/about-us/general-information/privacy-policy

All concerts and events through June 13, 2021 are cancelled. Learn more about our response to COVID-19. Support the Philharmonic by donating your tickets.
The New York Philharmonic
Pages don't look right?
You are using a browser that does not support the technology used on our website.
Please select a different browser or use your phone or tablet to access our site.
Download: Firefox | Chrome | Safari
If you're using Internet Explorer, please update to the latest version.
All concerts and events through June 13, 2021 are cancelled. Learn more about our response to COVID-19. Support the Philharmonic by donating your tickets.
(0)
Home
Concerts & Tickets
Calendar
Subscriptions
Explore Our Events
Plan Your Visit
How to Prepare
Getting Here
Last Updated May 2018
Thank you for visiting the New York Philharmonic!
We at the New York Philharmonic value your privacy and are committed to protecting the information you share with us. We have prepared this policy statement to explain how we collect, process, and share that information online.
What information does this Privacy Policy cover?
This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information collected on websites, mobile applications, or controlled widgets embedded in communication platforms with a link to this Privacy Policy (“Sites”).
By “Personal Information,” we mean information that identifies you personally. This Policy does not apply to any other information collected by the New York Philharmonic through any other means. This Policy also doesn’t apply to any Site maintained or operated by other companies or linked to our Site. It covers how we collect, use, and share that Personal Information as of the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.
You Consent to Transfer Your Personal Information to the United States
The New York Philharmonic is based in the United States. If you decide to use this Site, your Personal Information may be transferred to the United States and processed according to the terms described in this Privacy Policy.
The laws in the United States may not be considered adequate by authorities in your home country.
If you prefer not to have your Personal Information transferred to the United States, don’t use this Site. Otherwise, by using this Site, you expressly consent and authorize the New York Philharmonic to transfer your Personal Information to destinations outside your home country as we see necessary to run our business, and process it according to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
What types of Personal Information do we collect about our online visitors?
Information You Provide. We generally collect only Personal
Information you voluntarily provide to us. We don't require you to give us Personal Information to access certain public areas of our Site. This is true unless you live in a country that defines Personal Information to include network identifiers like your Internet Protocol addresses. For some secure areas of our Site, however, we require you to provide Personal Information when you use specific features. For example, we collect Personal Information from you when you:
• Ask to register for an account with us;
• Access subscriber services;
•	Purchase tickets or merchandise;
•	Donate to our organization;
•	Exchange tickets or FlexPasses;
•	Join our e-mail club; and
•	Participate in contests or surveys.
This Personal Information, for example, may include your:
•	Name;
•	Postal or billing address;
•	E-mail address;
•	Telephone or mobile number;
•	Payment card information;
•	Location via IP address;
•	Device being used (for our mobile site); and
•	Previous shopping history with New York Philharmonic.
Additionally, we may ask you to provide additional demographic information, such as income level and gender. This is optional, and we ask for it only so we may provide a more personalized and meaningful experience on our site.
If you cannot or choose not to provide us with the Personal Information we reasonably require, we may be unable to provide you with the certain information or services you have requested.
Information Collected Through Technology.
We also obtain information in other ways through technology.
Some of this information may be linked to you personally. This information helps our Site function correctly and supports the work we do to understand the needs of our customers.
Access logs.
We automatically collect and compile certain types of anonymous information from you whenever you interact with our Site to deliver the products you request from us and help improve your overall experience. These “access logs” enable us to make our Site more useful to you. The information automatically collected does not generally contain anything that can identify you personally. We log the following information:
•	The date of your visit;
•	The time you arrive and the length of your visit;
•	The browser you use; and
•	The IP address of your computer you used to visit our site.
Cookies. Like many other websites, we store “cookies” and other web-based files on user devices to get certain types of information when your web browser accesses our Site. We use a variety of third-party services to help provide our services, and to help us understand the use of our services. These third-party service providers may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. These cookies are not generally used to identify an individual; they’re used for statistical purposes, for example, in providing you with advertisements that are more relevant to your interests. Some of the information gleaned from third party cookies will be aggregated with other anonymous information for statistical purposes. The third party companies that generate these cookies have their own privacy policies, and we don't have access to this information. Other than allowing them to be served, we have no role to play in these cookies.
Pixel Tags. The New York Philharmonic uses pixel tags to gather information about the e-mails we send to our users. Pixel tags are tiny graphic files, not visible to the human eye, that are included in our HTML-encoded e-mail messages. When that message is opened in an HTML-capable e-mail program, the recipient's computer will access our e-mail provider's server to retrieve the pixel tag file, allowing us to record and store, along with your e-mail address, the date and time the recipient viewed the message, and other standard logging information.
The pixel tag also may see or read cookies.
For more information about cookies, see the section above on “Cookies.”
Device Information. Depending on the permissions you’ve granted and other factors, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device when you download or use apps created by our Site, including a unique identifier for your device.
We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, certain player search results, and other personalized content.
Examples of the device information we collect include:
•	Attributes such as the operating system, hardware version, device settings, file and software names and types, battery and signal strength, and device identifiers.
•	Device locations, including specific geographic locations, such as through GPS, Bluetooth, or WiFi signals.
•	Connection information such as the name of your mobile operator or ISP, browser type, language and time zone, mobile phone number and IP address.
Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services, and we encourage you to contact your device manufacturer for detailed instructions on how to do that.
Payment Information. If you purchase a product on our Site, we will collect payment card information from you, including your name, expiration date, authentication code, and billing and shipping address. We will securely transmit this information consistent with payment card industry rules to the appropriate payment facilitators. We may offer you the option to save information about the method and choice of payment on our Site. If you save this payment card information on our Site, you will be able to add, delete, or modify that information at any time using your account settings.
Do we advertise online?
We advertise in a number of ways, including online through managed social media presences, and on other unaffiliated sites and mobile applications. To understand how our advertising campaigns are performing, we may collect certain information via our Site through our advertising service providers. We or our vendors use several common online tracking tools to collect this information, such as browser cookies, web beacons and other, similar technologies.
The information we collect includes IP addresses, the number of page visits, pages viewed via our Site, search engine referrals, browsing activities over time and across other websites following your visit to our Site, and responses to advertisements and promotions on the websites and applications where we advertise.
We also use certain information to:
•	 Present tailored ads, including banner ads and splash ads that appear as you log-in or off of your online accounts via our Site;
•	Identify new visitors to our Site;
•	Recognize returning visitors;
•	Advertise on other websites and mobile applications not affiliated with us;
•	Better understand our audience, customers, or other Site visitors; and
•	Determine whether you might be interested in new products or services.
Controlling Our Tracking Tools. Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies. How you do so, however, depends on your browser and the type of cookie. Certain browsers can be set to reject all browser cookies. If you configure your computer to block all cookies, you may disrupt certain web page features, and limit the functionality we can provide when you visit or use our Site. If you block or delete cookies, not all of the tracking that we have described in this policy will stop. Some browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These browser features are still not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals.
Controlling Online Interest-Based Ads. We sometimes work with online advertising vendors to provide you with relevant and useful ads.
This may include ads served on or through our Site. This may also include ads served on other companies’ websites. These ads may be based on information collected by us or third parties. For example, your postal code may be used to target an ad for people in your area. These ads may also be based on your activities on our Site or on third party websites.
For more information about our ad service provider and its cookies, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, you may visit http://optout.aboutads.info/#! In addition, users may prevent Google’s collection of data generated by your use of the Site (including your IP address) by downloading and installing a Browser Plugin available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.
How do we use and share your Personal Information?
Whatever the purpose may be – whether we share with service providers or other external entities – we only process and share your Personal Information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. When we disclose Personal Information to external entities to perform support services for us, they may access your Personal Information only for the purposes of performing those support services. We may also use what we know about you to offer you other products and services. We may combine your online information with information collected from offline sources or information we already have. We may also use and disclose certain Personal Information to our corporate affiliates and others for any purpose allowed by law.
New York Philharmonic Activities. We may use and disclose your Personal Information to others to:
•	Respond to your questions, complaints, or reviews of our product or services;
•	Administer contests, promotions, or surveys;
•	Comply with applicable law, obey judicial orders, cooperate with law enforcement authorities, or prevent any suspected illegal activities;
•	Help us run our business; or
•	For any other everyday business purposes, such as product development and Site administration.
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This information is not linked to any Personal Information you provide, nor can it be used to identify any individual person.
We use information you provide to us to contact you about offers from the New York Philharmonic. Occasionally, we trade mailing lists with other non-profit and cultural organizations for promotional purposes. E-mail addresses and phone numbers are never shared. To opt out, send an e-mail to unsubscribe@nyphil.org.
Authorized Service Providers.
We use other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Those functions include payment card processors, shipping vendors, call-center support, analyzing or hosting data on cloud-based servers, and other companies that help us improve our products and services. We may disclose your Personal Information to these companies and other individuals performing services in the United States.
Sale of the Businesses.
If we sell all or part of our business, Personal Information may be transferred to the purchaser in connection with that transaction.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to include contractual provisions that require the purchaser to treat your Personal Information consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Other Disclosures. We may otherwise disclose Personal Information as permitted or required by law, when we believe in good faith it is necessary for safety purposes, required for legal reporting, or to protect our legal rights, enforce any applicable rules, or protect the rights of others. We may also disclose Personal Information to our auditors, legal advisors, or to respond to a subpoena.
We may also aggregate information that we gather about you (e.g., online sales, traffic patterns) and provide these statistics to others in aggregate form.
What choices do you have about the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information?
When you create an account with us, you have an opportunity to select your marketing preferences, and “opt out” of having your information used for marketing related activities.
You can also log back in to your account to opt-out and update your marketing preferences at any time.
Even after you opt-out or update your marketing preferences, please allow us sufficient time to process your marketing preferences.
It may take up to 10 days to process your e-mail related requests, and up to 30 days for all other marketing-related requests.
And even after you’ve opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us, we may still contact you for transactional or informational purposes.
These include, for example, customer service issues, returns or product-related inquiries, surveys or recalls, or any questions regarding a specific order.
We may occasionally send e-mails to those who have provided their e-mail addresses to us. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt out of receiving these communications by logging into your account (nyphil.org/login) and updating your communication preferences. With each e-mail, you also have the option to opt out of receiving future e-mails by clicking “Unsubscribe.”
You may also opt out by contacting us at:
New York Philharmonic
Attn.: Marketing Department
10 Lincoln Center Plaza, New York, NY 10023
unsubscribe@nyphil.org
What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard your Personal Information?
The security and confidentiality of your Personal Information matters to us.
That’s why we have technical, administrative, and physical controls in place to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure.
For example, we encrypt payment card information you submit to us using Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) technology that helps protect information during transport to our Site.
Of course, we transmit the entire payment card number to the appropriate credit card company through our payment processing vendor during order processing in accordance with payment card rules.
We also review our security procedures periodically to consider appropriate new technology and updated methods.
Even so, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measure is ever perfect or impenetrable.
How can you access, update, or block your Personal Information?
If your Personal Information changes or if you wish to change your preferences with regard to the use of your Personal Information, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide a way to correct, update, or remove the Personal Information provided to us. This can be done in two ways:
•	Simply log in to nyphil.org/login, click on “My Account,” and make the appropriate changes directly.
•	Send postal mail to Customer Relations, 10 Lincoln Center Plaza, New York, NY 10023, containing the changes you'd like for us to make.
In certain jurisdictions, such as the European Union, you may have the right to access, correct, port, or even erase the data we have about you. To make such a request, contact us at privacy@nyphil.org or write to us at the address above.
Please note that Personal Information may still be retained in accordance with our Record Retention Policy or to the extent necessary to comply with applicable law, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Minors and Children Under 13
Our Site is not generally intended for minors, and we do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use any Personal Information from children under the age of 13.
Certain portions of our Site, however, include content specifically designed for young musicians intended as an educational resource to be used in classrooms.
Several activities in those areas allow users to email certain content to a friend using send-a-friend features.
We have configured this feature to discard the email address from our systems once the email is sent, and we do not retain, share, or disclose that information with others.
If you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, please alert us at privacy@nyphil.org or write to us. We will take prompt steps to remove it from our systems.
Education Department
New York Philharmonic
132 West 65th Street
New York, NY 10023
(212) 875-5732
How can you file a complaint, ask questions, or send us comments about this Privacy Policy?
If you have any questions, have a complaint, or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, e-mail us at privacy@nyphil.org or call or write to us.
We will investigate your complaint, and use reasonable efforts to respond to you as soon as possible.
Our postal address is:
New York Philharmonic
Attn.: Marketing Department
10 Lincoln Center Plaza, New York, NY 10023
privacy@nyphil.org
How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material change in how we collect, use, disclose, or otherwise process Personal Information, we will post an updated Privacy Policy on our Site. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective 10 days after our posting of the updated Privacy Policy. Where required to do so by law, we may seek your prior consent to any material changes we make to this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with our Privacy Policy changes, you may de-activate your account at any time.
New York Philharmonic Privacy Policy
Last Updated May 2018
Thank you for visiting the New York Philharmonic!
We at the New York Philharmonic value your privacy and are committed to protecting the information you share with us. We have prepared this policy statement to explain how we collect, process, and share that information online.
What information does this Privacy Policy cover?
This Privacy Policy applies to Personal Information collected on websites, mobile applications, or controlled widgets embedded in communication platforms with a link to this Privacy Policy (“Sites”).
By “Personal Information,” we mean information that identifies you personally. This Policy does not apply to any other information collected by the New York Philharmonic through any other means. This Policy also doesn’t apply to any Site maintained or operated by other companies or linked to our Site. It covers how we collect, use, and share that Personal Information as of the date that this Privacy Policy is posted.
You Consent to Transfer Your Personal Information to the United States
The New York Philharmonic is based in the United States. If you decide to use this Site, your Personal Information may be transferred to the United States and processed according to the terms described in this Privacy Policy.
The laws in the United States may not be considered adequate by authorities in your home country.
If you prefer not to have your Personal Information transferred to the United States, don’t use this Site. Otherwise, by using this Site, you expressly consent and authorize the New York Philharmonic to transfer your Personal Information to destinations outside your home country as we see necessary to run our business, and process it according to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
What types of Personal Information do we collect about our online visitors?
Information You Provide. We generally collect only Personal
Information you voluntarily provide to us. We don't require you to give us Personal Information to access certain public areas of our Site. This is true unless you live in a country that defines Personal Information to include network identifiers like your Internet Protocol addresses. For some secure areas of our Site, however, we require you to provide Personal Information when you use specific features. For example, we collect Personal Information from you when you:
• Ask to register for an account with us;
• Access subscriber services;
•	Purchase tickets or merchandise;
•	Donate to our organization;
•	Exchange tickets or FlexPasses;
•	Join our e-mail club; and
•	Participate in contests or surveys.
This Personal Information, for example, may include your:
•	Name;
•	Postal or billing address;
•	E-mail address;
•	Telephone or mobile number;
•	Payment card information;
•	Location via IP address;
•	Device being used (for our mobile site); and
•	Previous shopping history with New York Philharmonic.
Additionally, we may ask you to provide additional demographic information, such as income level and gender. This is optional, and we ask for it only so we may provide a more personalized and meaningful experience on our site.
If you cannot or choose not to provide us with the Personal Information we reasonably require, we may be unable to provide you with the certain information or services you have requested.
Information Collected Through Technology.
We also obtain information in other ways through technology.
Some of this information may be linked to you personally. This information helps our Site function correctly and supports the work we do to understand the needs of our customers.
Access logs.
We automatically collect and compile certain types of anonymous information from you whenever you interact with our Site to deliver the products you request from us and help improve your overall experience. These “access logs” enable us to make our Site more useful to you. The information automatically collected does not generally contain anything that can identify you personally. We log the following information:
•	The date of your visit;
•	The time you arrive and the length of your visit;
•	The browser you use; and
•	The IP address of your computer you used to visit our site.
Cookies. Like many other websites, we store “cookies” and other web-based files on user devices to get certain types of information when your web browser accesses our Site. We use a variety of third-party services to help provide our services, and to help us understand the use of our services. These third-party service providers may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. These cookies are not generally used to identify an individual; they’re used for statistical purposes, for example, in providing you with advertisements that are more relevant to your interests. Some of the information gleaned from third party cookies will be aggregated with other anonymous information for statistical purposes. The third party companies that generate these cookies have their own privacy policies, and we don't have access to this information. Other than allowing them to be served, we have no role to play in these cookies.
Pixel Tags. The New York Philharmonic uses pixel tags to gather information about the e-mails we send to our users. Pixel tags are tiny graphic files, not visible to the human eye, that are included in our HTML-encoded e-mail messages. When that message is opened in an HTML-capable e-mail program, the recipient's computer will access our e-mail provider's server to retrieve the pixel tag file, allowing us to record and store, along with your e-mail address, the date and time the recipient viewed the message, and other standard logging information.
The pixel tag also may see or read cookies.
For more information about cookies, see the section above on “Cookies.”
Device Information. Depending on the permissions you’ve granted and other factors, we may receive information about your location and your mobile device when you download or use apps created by our Site, including a unique identifier for your device.
We may use this information to provide you with location-based services, such as advertising, certain player search results, and other personalized content.
Examples of the device information we collect include:
•	Attributes such as the operating system, hardware version, device settings, file and software names and types, battery and signal strength, and device identifiers.
•	Device locations, including specific geographic locations, such as through GPS, Bluetooth, or WiFi signals.
•	Connection information such as the name of your mobile operator or ISP, browser type, language and time zone, mobile phone number and IP address.
Most mobile devices allow you to turn off location services, and we encourage you to contact your device manufacturer for detailed instructions on how to do that.
Payment Information. If you purchase a product on our Site, we will collect payment card information from you, including your name, expiration date, authentication code, and billing and shipping address. We will securely transmit this information consistent with payment card industry rules to the appropriate payment facilitators. We may offer you the option to save information about the method and choice of payment on our Site. If you save this payment card information on our Site, you will be able to add, delete, or modify that information at any time using your account settings.
Do we advertise online?
We advertise in a number of ways, including online through managed social media presences, and on other unaffiliated sites and mobile applications. To understand how our advertising campaigns are performing, we may collect certain information via our Site through our advertising service providers. We or our vendors use several common online tracking tools to collect this information, such as browser cookies, web beacons and other, similar technologies.
The information we collect includes IP addresses, the number of page visits, pages viewed via our Site, search engine referrals, browsing activities over time and across other websites following your visit to our Site, and responses to advertisements and promotions on the websites and applications where we advertise.
We also use certain information to:
•	 Present tailored ads, including banner ads and splash ads that appear as you log-in or off of your online accounts via our Site;
•	Identify new visitors to our Site;
•	Recognize returning visitors;
•	Advertise on other websites and mobile applications not affiliated with us;
•	Better understand our audience, customers, or other Site visitors; and
•	Determine whether you might be interested in new products or services.
Controlling Our Tracking Tools. Your browser may give you the ability to control cookies. How you do so, however, depends on your browser and the type of cookie. Certain browsers can be set to reject all browser cookies. If you configure your computer to block all cookies, you may disrupt certain web page features, and limit the functionality we can provide when you visit or use our Site. If you block or delete cookies, not all of the tracking that we have described in this policy will stop. Some browsers have a “Do Not Track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. These browser features are still not uniform, so we are not currently set up to respond to those signals.
Controlling Online Interest-Based Ads. We sometimes work with online advertising vendors to provide you with relevant and useful ads.
This may include ads served on or through our Site. This may also include ads served on other companies’ websites. These ads may be based on information collected by us or third parties. For example, your postal code may be used to target an ad for people in your area. These ads may also be based on your activities on our Site or on third party websites.
For more information about our ad service provider and its cookies, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, you may visit http://optout.aboutads.info/#! In addition, users may prevent Google’s collection of data generated by your use of the Site (including your IP address) by downloading and installing a Browser Plugin available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en.
How do we use and share your Personal Information?
Whatever the purpose may be – whether we share with service providers or other external entities – we only process and share your Personal Information to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and our legitimate business objectives. When we disclose Personal Information to external entities to perform support services for us, they may access your Personal Information only for the purposes of performing those support services. We may also use what we know about you to offer you other products and services. We may combine your online information with information collected from offline sources or information we already have. We may also use and disclose certain Personal Information to our corporate affiliates and others for any purpose allowed by law.
New York Philharmonic Activities. We may use and disclose your Personal Information to others to:
•	Respond to your questions, complaints, or reviews of our product or services;
•	Administer contests, promotions, or surveys;
•	Comply with applicable law, obey judicial orders, cooperate with law enforcement authorities, or prevent any suspected illegal activities;
•	Help us run our business; or
•	For any other everyday business purposes, such as product development and Site administration.
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This information is not linked to any Personal Information you provide, nor can it be used to identify any individual person.
We use information you provide to us to contact you about offers from the New York Philharmonic. Occasionally, we trade mailing lists with other non-profit and cultural organizations for promotional purposes. E-mail addresses and phone numbers are never shared. To opt out, send an e-mail to unsubscribe@nyphil.org.
Authorized Service Providers.
We use other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Those functions include payment card processors, shipping vendors, call-center support, analyzing or hosting data on cloud-based servers, and other companies that help us improve our products and services. We may disclose your Personal Information to these companies and other individuals performing services in the United States.
Sale of the Businesses.
If we sell all or part of our business, Personal Information may be transferred to the purchaser in connection with that transaction.
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to include contractual provisions that require the purchaser to treat your Personal Information consistent with this Privacy Policy.
Other Disclosures. We may otherwise disclose Personal Information as permitted or required by law, when we believe in good faith it is necessary for safety purposes, required for legal reporting, or to protect our legal rights, enforce any applicable rules, or protect the rights of others. We may also disclose Personal Information to our auditors, legal advisors, or to respond to a subpoena.
We may also aggregate information that we gather about you (e.g., online sales, traffic patterns) and provide these statistics to others in aggregate form.
What choices do you have about the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information?
When you create an account with us, you have an opportunity to select your marketing preferences, and “opt out” of having your information used for marketing related activities.
You can also log back in to your account to opt-out and update your marketing preferences at any time.
Even after you opt-out or update your marketing preferences, please allow us sufficient time to process your marketing preferences.
It may take up to 10 days to process your e-mail related requests, and up to 30 days for all other marketing-related requests.
And even after you’ve opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us, we may still contact you for transactional or informational purposes.
These include, for example, customer service issues, returns or product-related inquiries, surveys or recalls, or any questions regarding a specific order.
We may occasionally send e-mails to those who have provided their e-mail addresses to us. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt out of receiving these communications by logging into your account (nyphil.org/login) and updating your communication preferences. With each e-mail, you also have the option to opt out of receiving future e-mails by clicking “Unsubscribe.”
You may also opt out by contacting us at:
New York Philharmonic
Attn.: Marketing Department
10 Lincoln Center Plaza, New York, NY 10023
unsubscribe@nyphil.org
What kinds of security measures do we take to safeguard your Personal Information?
The security and confidentiality of your Personal Information matters to us.
That’s why we have technical, administrative, and physical controls in place to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, and disclosure.
For example, we encrypt payment card information you submit to us using Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”) technology that helps protect information during transport to our Site.
Of course, we transmit the entire payment card number to the appropriate credit card company through our payment processing vendor during order processing in accordance with payment card rules.
We also review our security procedures periodically to consider appropriate new technology and updated methods.
Even so, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measure is ever perfect or impenetrable.
How can you access, update, or block your Personal Information?
If your Personal Information changes or if you wish to change your preferences with regard to the use of your Personal Information, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to provide a way to correct, update, or remove the Personal Information provided to us. This can be done in two ways:
•	Simply log in to nyphil.org/login, click on “My Account,” and make the appropriate changes directly.
•	Send postal mail to Customer Relations, 10 Lincoln Center Plaza, New York, NY 10023, containing the changes you'd like for us to make.
In certain jurisdictions, such as the European Union, you may have the right to access, correct, port, or even erase the data we have about you. To make such a request, contact us at privacy@nyphil.org or write to us at the address above.
Please note that Personal Information may still be retained in accordance with our Record Retention Policy or to the extent necessary to comply with applicable law, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Minors and Children Under 13
Our Site is not generally intended for minors, and we do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use any Personal Information from children under the age of 13.
Certain portions of our Site, however, include content specifically designed for young musicians intended as an educational resource to be used in classrooms.
Several activities in those areas allow users to email certain content to a friend using send-a-friend features.
We have configured this feature to discard the email address from our systems once the email is sent, and we do not retain, share, or disclose that information with others.
If you learn that your child has provided us with Personal Information without your consent, please alert us at privacy@nyphil.org or write to us. We will take prompt steps to remove it from our systems.
Education Department
New York Philharmonic
132 West 65th Street
New York, NY 10023
(212) 875-5732
How can you file a complaint, ask questions, or send us comments about this Privacy Policy?
If you have any questions, have a complaint, or wish to send us comments about this Privacy Policy, e-mail us at privacy@nyphil.org or call or write to us.
We will investigate your complaint, and use reasonable efforts to respond to you as soon as possible.
Our postal address is:
New York Philharmonic
Attn.: Marketing Department
10 Lincoln Center Plaza, New York, NY 10023
privacy@nyphil.org
How will you know if we amend this Privacy Policy?
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material change in how we collect, use, disclose, or otherwise process Personal Information, we will post an updated Privacy Policy on our Site. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective 10 days after our posting of the updated Privacy Policy. Where required to do so by law, we may seek your prior consent to any material changes we make to this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with our Privacy Policy changes, you may de-activate your account at any time.
×
Join our community
Contact Us
(212) 875-5656
David Geffen Hall
10 Lincoln Center Plaza
New York, NY 10023-6970
Privacy Policy
The New York Philharmonic is a 501(c)(3) non-profit organization | EIN: 13-1664054
Support the New York Philharmonic
We need your help: support both digital performances and experimental new live concert formats like NY Phil Bandwagon.
